The Comeback: Tegan Nox is a documentary film directed by None.
Tegan Nox’s WWE dream almost ended early due to a pair of serious knee injuries.
Witness the highs and lows of her journey back to the ring.
Self / Tegan Nox, played by Steffanie Newell.
Self / Candice LeRae, played by Candice LeRae.
Self, played by Shayna Baszler.
Self, played by Glen Joseph.
Self / Dakota Kai, played by Cheree Crowley.
Self / Robbie Brookside, played by Robert Brooks.
Natalie Katherine Neidhart-Wilson (née Neidhart; born May 27,
1982) is a Canadian-American professional wrestler.
She is signed to WWE, where she performs on the Raw
brand under the ring name Natalya.
She also wrestles on the independent circuit under her
real name, stylized as Nattie Neidhart.
She is a two-time women's world champion, having won the WWE Divas
Championship and WWE SmackDown Women's Championship once each.
She is also a former one-time WWE Women's Tag Team Champion (with Tamina).
A third generation wrestler, Neidhart is a member of the Hart wrestling family through her mother,
and is also the daughter of Hart Foundation member and Hall of Famer Jim Neidhart.
She trained in the Hart family Dungeon under the
tutelage of her uncles Ross and Bruce Hart.
From 2000 to 2001, she worked for the Matrats promotion,
before debuting for Stampede Wrestling in 2003.
In 2004 and 2005, she wrestled abroad in England and Japan.
She became the inaugural Stampede Women's Pacific Champion in 2005,
and won the SuperGirls Championship the following year.
In 2007, Neidhart signed with WWE and spent time in Deep South Wrestling (DSW), Ohio Valley
Wrestling (OVW), and Florida Championship Wrestling (FCW) developmental territories.
While in FCW, she managed her cousin, Harry Smith, and her husband, T.J.
She debuted on the main roster in 2008, allying herself with Victoria.
The following year, she and Wilson were joined by
Smith to form The Hart Dynasty.
In 2010, Neidhart won the Divas Championship.
In 2017, she became the SmackDown Women's Champion
after defeating Naomi at SummerSlam.
She is the first woman in WWE history to hold both the Divas
Championship and the SmackDown Women's Championship.
From 2013 to 2019, Neidhart appeared in the reality television series Total
Divas, the sole consistent main cast member across all nine seasons.
She has set six records as recognized by the Guinness Book of World Records for female WWE wrestlers – most pay-per-view
appearances, most matches, most wins, most Raw matches, most SmackDown matches, and most WrestleMania matches.
Neidhart is the longest-tenured female WWE wrestler,
actively being with the company since 2007.
The film explores themes of comeback, knee injury, sports injury, pro wrestling.